<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">InnerSpace</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>


    <string name="About">Mind plays the important role in living our life healthier and in our well-being.\n\nWhen mind is healthy we can cope with every challenges in life and handle stress of work.\n\nWe keep our feelings to ourselves which becomes toxic which is not good for our mental health.\n\nCome let\'s have a chat to know more about your mental health.\n</string>
    <string name="adddd" translatable="false">Tips for keeping your mental health Good\n1. Track gratitude and achievement with a journal. Include three things you were grateful for and three things you were able to accomplish each day.\n 2. Start your day with a cup of coffee. Coffee consumption is linked to lower rates of depression. If you can\’t drink coffee because of the caffeine, try another good-for-you drink like green tea. \n3. Set up a getaway. It could be camping with friends or a trip to the tropics. The act of planning a vacation and having something to look forward to can boost your overall happiness for up to 8 weeks! \n4 Work your strengths. Do something you\'re good at to build self-confidence, then tackle a tougher task. \n5. Keep it cool for a good night\'s sleep. The optimal temperature for sleep is between 60 and 67 degrees Fahrenheit. \n6. You don\'t have to see the whole staircase, just take the first step. - Martin Luther King, Jr. Think of something in your life you want to improve, and figure out what you can do to take a step in the right direction.\n 7. Experiment with a new recipe, write a poem, paint or try a Pinterest project. Creative expression and overall well-being are linked.\n 8. Show some love to someone in your life. Close, quality, relationships are key for a happy, healthy life.\n 9. Boost brainpower by treating yourself to a couple pieces of dark chocolate every few days. The flavanoids, caffeine, and theobromine in chocolate are thought to work together to improve alertness and mental skills. \n10. “There is no greater agony than bearing an untold story inside of you.” -Maya Angelou.\n If you have personal experience with mental illness or recovery, share on Twitter, Instagram and Tumblr with #mentalillnessfeelslike.\n Check out what other people are saying here. And You Can follow the above Tips and you can give the test again After 2 week\n\n\n</string>
    <string name="suicide">Treatment There are various methods for managing mental health problems. Treatment is highly individual, and what works for one person may not work for another. Some strategies or treatments are more successful in combination with others. A person living with a chronic mental disorder may choose different options at various stages in their life. The individual needs to work closely with a doctor who can help them identify their needs and provide them with suitable treatment. Biological factors Having a gene with links to a mental health disorder, such as depression or schizophrenia, does not guarantee that a condition will develop. Likewise, people without related genes or a family history of mental illness can still have mental health issues. Common mental health disorders The most common types of mental illness are as follows: \n• anxiety disorders \n• mood disorders\n • schizophrenia disorder Call 911 or the local emergency number, or text TALK to 741741 to communicate with a trained crisis counselor.\n Central government has created a helpline number 1800-599-0019 called ‘Kiran’ And this will help you to Contact Doctors.\n</string>


</resources>